Guide to the Child Study Center, School of Medicine, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Donald J. Cohen as director, circa 1983-2001; Accession 2003-A-024
  - Benhaven Title XIX Program (Box 3)
  - Benhaven: PEW Proposal (Box 3)
  - Benhaven Pharmacy Meeting (Box 3)
  - Benhaven: Letter to the Editor (Box 3)
  - Benhaven: Proposed Project Plan, Sau-Fong Siu (Box 3)
  - Benhaven: The School That Works, Stephen Rudley, Cynthia Lynes (Box 3)
  - Benhaven: Video therapy: A Project for the Education of Autistic Child. (Box 3)
  - Berger Fellows (Box 3)
  - Bialystok (Box 4)
  - Bialystoker Home and infirmary for the Aged (Box 4)
  - Blueberry Treatment Center (Box 4)
  - Blue Cross-Blue Shield Mental Health Delivery (Box 4)
  - Boys and Girls Club of America (Box 4)
  - Boys Town (Box 4)
  - Brain Research (Box 4)
  - Brandeis University, Waltham, MA (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Candidates for Presidency (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: "Looking for Another Way Out" and Looking for Another Way In" For Justice. (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Elizabeth Handler, President Brandeis University (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Inauguration Plans with Evelyn Handler, Oct 9, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Bylaws of Brandeis University (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: NEJS Department (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Student Housing Project (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Alumni Achievement Dinner, October 19, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Academic Affairs Committee, Oct 25, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Academic Affairs Committee, December 16, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: September 28, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Alumni Trustee Board Nomination (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Board Meeting, Boston, MA. October 31 to November 1, 1986. (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Board of Directors Meeting May 17, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Brandeis: Board Meeting, April 18, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Bush Center, Progress Report 2000-2001 (Box 5)
  - Bush Center (Box 5)
  - Bush Center Social Policy September 25, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Yale-Bush Network Progress Report 1983-84 (Box 5)
  - Children's Seashore House. Children's Mental Health All. Project Meeting November 10/Penn Tower/U of PA (Box 5)
  - Canada (Box 5)
  - Chapel Haven (Box 5)
  - Charter Schools (Box 5)
  - Childhood Personality Scoring Sheet (Box 5)
  - C. Miscellaneous (Box 5)
  - Calvin Hill Day Care Center (Box 5)
  - Calvin Hill Board Meeting, June 14, 1984 (8: pm) (Box 5)
  - Career High School (Box 5)
  - Carnegie Council on Children (Box 5)
  - Case Western Reserve Site Visit, 9/25-9/26, 1989 (Box 5)
  - CBS Charles Kuralt Freud (Box 5)
  - CCRC Program and CCRC Site Visit, March 25, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Center For Children with Special Needs (Box 5)
  - Chapel Haven (Box 5)
  - Chestnut Lodge (Box 6)
  - Child Abuse and Neglect: Panel on Abuse and Neglect and Abuse (Box 6)
  - Childhood Autism (Box 6)
  - Children's Research Center Consortium, January 11, 1995 (Cornel Club- 6 East 44thStreet. (Box 6)
  - Connecticut Voices for Children Awards and Publications (Box 6)
  - Convention on the Rights of the Child (Box 6)
  - Child Development/Community Policing (Box 6)
  - Child Development Institute of Connecticut (Box 6)
  - Clifford Beers Lecture, April 6, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Clifford Beers Lecture, June 3, 1988 (Box 6)
  - Clifford Beers Lecture, March 24, 1987 (1) (Box 6)
  - Clifford Beers Lecture, March 24, 1987 (2) (Box 6)
  - Clifford Beers Lecture, May 6, 1991, Senator Jay Rockefeller (Box 6)
  - Clifford Beers Anniversary, November 3, 1988 (Box 6)
  - Clifford W. Beers., Guidance Clinic, Inc., New Haven CT. (Box 6)
  - Clifford Beers Lecture, September 24, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Clifford Beers Lecture, October 14, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Clifford Beers Applicants (Box 6)
  - Hillary Rodham Clinton (Box 6)
  - Comer School Development 30thAnniversary (Box 7)
  - Community Mental Health Center (Box 7)
  - Community Renaissance Fellow Program (Box 7)
  - Compass (Box 7)
  - Connecticut Association for Retarded Citizens (Box 7)
  - Connecticut Commission on Children, December 5, 1991, Hartford (Box 7)
  - Connecticut Commission on Children: Task Force on National Commission on Children Report (Box 7)
  - Connecticut Council of Child and Adolescent Psychiatrists (Box 7)
  - Alphabetical Roll of the Senate and House (Box 7)
  - Connecticut General Assembly, New Haven Delegation (Box 7)
  - State of Connecticut Health Care Discussion Group (Box 7)
  - Connecticut Health Plan (Box 7)
  - Connecticut General Assembly List of Legislators: 1991 (Box 7)
  - Connecticut Mental Health Center (Box 7)
  - Connecticut Mental Health Center Credential Process (Box 7)
  - The Consultation Center (Box 7)
  - Clinical Services (Box 7)
  - Nancy Cotton Visit (Box 7)
  - Crises Intervention Committee (Box 7)
  - D. Miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Dwight Edgewood West River: Organizational Players (Box 7)
  - Daiichi Pharmaceutical Co. December 4. (Box 7)
  - Mayor John C. Daniels (Box 7)
  - Day Care (Box 7)
  - Crime Bill (Box 7)
  - Department of Children and Families (Box 8)
  - Department of Mental Retardation (DMR), Policy Issues and Reports (Box 8)
  - Kids Killing Kids, Office of the Mayor, City Hall, 125 Church Street, March 28, 1994 (Box 8)
  - City of New Haven (Box 8)
  - Detention Center (Box 8)
  - Development Office School Of Medicine (Box 8)
  - Development Office Yale University (Box 8)
  - Development and Psychopathology (Box 8)
  - Companion Instruments, Parental Style (Box 8)
  - Discovery Health TV (Box 8)
  - Discovery Toys, Nashville Convention 95, Nashville Tennessee, February 8, 9, 19, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Discovery Toys, Self Esteem Awards, January, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Senator Christopher Dodd Visit, February 25, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Senator Christopher Dodd, Child Study Center, June 20, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Kids and Guns, Washington, D. C. July 23, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Senator Christopher Dodd "Summary of Child and Family Services and Law Enforcement Partnership Act". (Box 8)
  - John Donaldson Visit, March 23, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Ann Donnellen Visit, January 21, 1983 (Box 8)
  - School Meeting, Superintendent Dow, February 11, 1987 (Box 8)
  - D.C.Y.S. Child Guidance Statistical Summary (Box 8)
  - Clonidine/Ritalin (Box 8)
  - Anafranil (Box 8)
  - Drugs: Anafranil (Box 8)
  - Clonidine (Box 8)
  - Debrisoquin (Box 8)
  - Despramine (Box 8)
  - Fenfluramine (Box 8)
  - Fluoxetine (Box 8)
  - BHT-920 (Box 8)
  - 5-Hydroxytrytophane (Box 8)
  - Hylorel, Pennwalt Pharmaceuticals (Box 8)
  - Pimozide (Box 8)
  - Prozac (Box 8)
  - Ritalin (Box 8)
  - Tofranil (Box 8)
  - Use of Tricyclic Drugs (Box 8)
  - DSM Task Force (Box 8)
  - DSM Text (Box 8)
  - SDM IV Diagnostic Classification (Box 8)
  - DSM-IV (Box 8)
  - "E" Miscellaneous (Box 9)
  - Edgewood School (Box 9)
  - Early Childhood Training Program (Box 9)
  - EBJ Board Meeting, September 5, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Edith B. Jackson Board Meeting, 6/21/84 Toddler Center (Box 9)
  - Forum On Education and Society (Box 9)
  - Forum On Education and Society, School Based Crises Intervention Model (Box 9)
  - Elm Haven (Box 9)
  - England File (Box 9)
  - Epstein David, The American Jewish Distribution Committee (Box 9)
  - Administrative Site Visit (Dr. Erlenmeyer-Kimling) June 13, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Exorcism Case (Box 9)
  - "F" Miscellaneous (Box 9)
  - Facilitated Communication (Box 9)
  - Facilitated Communication (An Experimental Assessment) (Box 9)
  - Facilities Planning (Box 10)
  - Faculty Practice (Box 10)
  - New Haven family Campus Initiative; Early Childhood and Family Support Action Plan June 1996 (Box 10)
  - Family Campus Initiatives (Box 10)
  - Family Campus (Box 10)
  - Family Support Service (Box 10)
  - Fellows Journal Club (Box 10)
  - Fighting Back (Box 10)
  - Footbridge (Box 10)
  - Forsenic Child Psychiatry Group In the CSC (Box 10)
  - Friends of Autistic Children and Adults, Inc. (herein after referred to as the "corporation") (Box 10)
  - Forum on Education and Society (Rockefeller) (Box 11)
  - Children and Violence Overview (Box 11)
  - Juvenile Justice System (Handbook) (Box 11)
  - Foster Care (Box 11)
  - FFRP: 25thAnniversary Meeting, May 4, 1979 (Box 11)
  - FFRP: Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Directors (Box 11)
  - FFRP Board of Directors Meeting Seven Springs Center, MT. Kisco, NY. June 5-6, 1981. (Box 11)
  - FFRP Board Meeting, October 29-31, 1977 Seven Springs Center, Mount Kisco, N. Y., Dr. Donald Cohen. (Box 11)
  - France (Box 11)
  - France: Autism Network (Box 11)
  - Letters of Recommendation, Richard Frank (Box 11)
  - Sherv Frazier Visit-Dinner, June 5, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Freud Panel, April, 1973 (Box 11)
  - The Freud Museum (Box 11)
  - "G" Miscellaneous I (Box 11)
  - "G" Miscellaneous II (Box 11)
  - Visit of Congressman Gephart (Box 11)
  - Gach Book Company, Lanning Donation of Books to Child Study Center (Box 11)
  - The Children of GAZA (Box 12)
  - Gesell, Arnold (Box 12)
  - Gesell, Gerhard (Box 12)
  - Gesell Institute (Box 12)
  - Gesell Archives, June 5, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Gesell/CSC Collaborations, Early Childhood Collaboration 1998 (Box 12)
  - Gesell Professorship (Box 12)
  - Gesell Professorship Brochure (Box 12)
  - Bart Giamatti (Box 12)
  - Grant Outlines (Box 13)
  - Group of 5 September (Autism Inserm) (Box 13)
  - Task Force on Tardive Dyskinesia Thomas Gualteri (Box 13)
  - "H" Miscellaneous I (Box 13)
  - "H" Miscellaneous II (Box 13)
  - Harkness Dormitory Guest Apartments (Box 13)
  - Oren Harman, Visitor/September 1977 (Box 13)
  - HCFA (Box 13)
  - Hadassah_Hebrew University, Hospital (Box 13)
  - David Hamburg, MD, Clifford Beers Lecture, May 12, 1993 (Box 13)
  - David Hamburg, MD, Retirement (Statement) (Box 13)
  - Handbook of Autism: Correspondence (Box 13)
  - Handbook of Autism: 2ndEdition (Box 13)
  - Dorothy Harman Peres Center (Box 13)
  - Harris Program Applicant (Box 14)
  - Hartman, Paul H. "Equipment for Development Diagnosis". (Box 14)
  - Haskell F. Norman Prize for Psychoanalytic Excellence (Box 14)
  - Judge Baker Children's Center Consortium's Technical Assistance Grant February 11, 1994 (Box 14)
  - Headstart/Public School Early Childhood Early Transition Demonstration Program (Box 14)
  - Headstart Transition Program (Box 14)
  - Comprehensive Child Development Program (Box 14)
  - Head Start Follow-up August 5, 1991 (Box 14)
  - Health Systems Agency of South Central Connecticut (Box 14)
  - Healthy Start (Box 14)
  - Hebrew Day School (Hecht, Rabbi) (Box 14)
  - High Meadows/CSC (Box 14)
  - Yale Hillel Foundation Year End Report, July 1, 1992-June 30 1993 and other reports and Correspondence (Box 14)
  - Art Issue Slifka Center (Box 14)
  - Hillel (Box 14)
  - Hillel: Correspondaence with prospects (Box 14)
  - Yale Hillel Board of Trustees, Legal issues and Documents (Box 14)
  - Hillel: Dinner: CT. Leadership Rose (Box 14)
  - Hillel Building Compaign, Wall Street Site (Box 14)
  - Hillel Plans (Box 14)
  - Hillel: Minutes, Budget, etc (Box 15)
  - Hillel/Slifica Meetings, June 15-17, 1992 (Box 15)
  - Board Members, Minutes, Budget (Box 15)
  - Hillel Letterhead (Box 15)
  - Hillel: Newspaper Clippings (Box 15)
  - Hillel, Yale University, Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Hillel Legal Issues (Box 15)
  - Hillel Board Meeting (Box 15)
  - Joseph Slifka Center for Jewish life at Yale (Box 15)
  - House of Representatives (Box 15)
  - Mental Health Law Project (James Hughes) (Box 15)
  - Human Rights Watch, (Ms. Jo Beckers) (Box 15)
  - NIMH Discussion Group on Child psychiatry Research, Oct 18, 1990 Chicago, 4:00 to 6:30 PM (AACP) (Box 15)
  - Hyde School (Box 15)
  - ISRCAP Membership Roster (Box 15)
  - IDX (Box 15)
  - Indonesia (Box 15)
  - Infant-Toddler Center (Box 16)
  - Institute of Living, Hank Schwartz (Box 16)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) (Miscellaneous Papers) (Box 16)
  - IOM Meeting, December 7, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Institute of Medicine Call for Nominations (Box 16)
  - Institute of Medicine 1993 Annual Meeting, October 17-19, 1993 (Box 16)
  - IOM Annual Meetings (Box 16)
  - IOM: Charter and Bylaws (Box 16)
  - IOM: Correspondence (Box 16)
  - IOM: Council Terms, 1990-92 (Box 16)
  - IOM: Candidate Proposals (Box 16)
  - Institute of Medicine, August 18-19, 1986, Washington D.C (Box 16)
  - Planning Meeting for "A Study on Youth Violence in School", December 7, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Mental Illness and Addictive Disorders (Box 16)
  - Institute of Medicine Proposals (I) (Box 16)
  - Institute of Medicine Proposals (II) (Box 16)
  - Sept, 1983: IOM Draft Report on ADAMHA Research Opportunities "Research on Ment. Illness and Addictive States: "(Barchas)" (Box 16)
  - IOM: Task Force for the Study of Research on Child and Adolescent Mental Disorders (Woods Hole: 8/28-31, 1988). (Box 16)
  - Institute of Medicine: Sterling Committee (Box 16)
  - IOM: Manpower (Box 16)
  - IOM: Background Reading (Box 16)
  - International Addresses: Australia (Box 16)
  - International Addresses: China (Box 16)
  - IACAPAP: Croatia (Box 16)
  - England (Box 16)
  - France (Box 16)
  - Germany (Box 16)
  - Holland (Box 16)
  - Indonesia (Box 16)
  - Nigeria (Box 16)
  - Weizman Institute Proposal (Teva Pharmaceuticals) (Box 16)
  - CSC/Israel (Youth Aliyah Collaboration) (Box 16)
  - TS Postmortem Brain Research (Box 16)
  - Israel Defense Force (Box 17)
  - TSA: Israel (Box 17)
  - IDF/CSC Collaboration (Box 17)
  - CSC/IDF Visit: October 20-23 (Box 17)
  - Israel, June 26 -July 15, 1991 (Box 17)
  - Military Life Questionnaire (Box 17)
  - The Psychosomatic Concept of "Stimulus Barrier In Psychoanalytic Theory". 30th Congress, Int. PSA Association. Jerusalem Aug 1977. (Box 17)
  - Israel: Addresses and Phone July 1991 (Box 17)
  - Israel Name and Addresses (Box 17)
  - Israel A-B (Box 17)
  - Israel C-D (Box 17)
  - Israel: E-L (Box 17)
  - Israel G-H (Box 17)
  - Israel I-J (Box 17)
  - Israel K (Box 17)
  - Israel L (Box 17)
  - Israel M-N (Box 17)
  - Israel O-P (Box 17)
  - Israel Q-R (Box 17)
  - Israel School Development (Box 17)
  - Israel S-T (Box 17)
  - Israel W-V (Box 17)
  - Israel X-Y=Z (Box 17)
  - Israeli-Palestinian Project (Box 17)
  - Child Study Center, Italian Conference, Oct. 13-14 (Box 17)
  - IL Telefono Azzurro (Box 17)
  - Italian Binational Collaboration (Box 17)
  - "J" Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - Journal of the International Association of Child and Adolescent Psychiatry and Allied Professions (Box 18)
  - JDC-Brookdale (Box 18)
  - Correspondence -Japan (Box 18)
  - Jewish Women International (Box 18)
  - B'Nai B'Rith Women (Box 18)
  - B'Nai B'Rith Meeting, New Orleans, LA, April 27-28, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Jewish Theological Seminary (Box 18)
  - Jewish Theological Seminary, October 28 and November 4 (Box 18)
  - Robert wood Johnson (Box 18)
  - Robert wood Johnson, Proposal (Box 18)
  - Robert wood Johnson Program (Box 18)
  - Robert wood Johnson Site Visit, September 27, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Robert wood Johnson Planning Meeting, July 13, 1989, Child Study Center (Box 18)
  - Robert wood Johnson Letter of Interest (Box 18)
  - Robert wood Johnson Site Visit June 4, 1985 (Box 18)
  - Dr. Goulder: Connecticut Department of Mental Health CMHC-CSC, Proposal for Research and Training Center (Focus, Dev. Aspects, Deafness) Proposal (Box 18)
  - Infant Health and Development Program (Box 18)
  - Judaic Studies Program at Yale (Box 18)
  - Judaic Studies, Yale University (Box 18)
  - Juvenile Justice Pilot Study (Box 18)
  - Juvenile Justice System and Children (Box 18)
  - "K" Miscellaneous I (Box 18)
  - "K" Miscellaneous II (Box 18)
  - Kosovo (Box 19)
  - Barry Kaufman: The Option Process (Box 19)
  - Ted Kennedy: Lead Program (Box 19)
  - Lead Project (Box 19)
  - David Pollack (United States Senate) (Box 19)
  - Killam's Point Conference Center Map (Box 19)
  - Child Psychiatry by: Moshe Yitzhak Stein, Kiryas Joel School (Box 19)
  - Reuven Kohen-Raz, Visit to CSC, January 22-31, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Korea (Box 19)
  - US Scientific Symposium-NIMH, Banglore, India, February 7-14, 1993 (Box 19)
  - Mr. Adrian Krieg, Wilder Company (Box 19)
  - Aaron B. Lerner Symposium, Yale Freshman Commons, June 22, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Lesch-Nyhan (Box 20)
  - Primary Care Center-Y-NHH, John Leventhal, MD (Box 20)
  - "L" Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Dean Neil Larsen, Quinnipiac College, December 11, 1995, 2:00-4:00 PM (Box 20)
  - Lithuania (Box 20)
  - The Honorable Michael Lawlor, State of Connecticut House Democrats (Box 20)
  - Howard Lamar (Box 20)
  - Susan Lambert, Visit to Child Study Center (Box 20)
  - Nathaniel Laor: Trauma Study (Box 20)
  - Michael Bruno Award (Box 20)
  - TSA: New York, Yale Club, January 9,10, 1994 (Box 21)
  - President Richard Levin (Box 21)
  - Professor and Mrs. Richard and Jane Levin (Box 21)
  - Sen. Joseph Lieberman (Box 21)
  - Senator Joseph Lieberman: Autism Bill (Box 21)
  - Sir James Lighthill (Box 21)
  - Lister, George Dr., Cardiovascular Research Institute, University of California Medical Center, Sanfrancisco (Box 21)
  - Littleton School Shooting (Box 21)
  - Linda Lorimer (Box 21)
  - New Haven Education Initiatives, Yale University (Box 21)
  - Medical Development for Israel, Inc., Mr. Jules Love (Box 21)
  - Lydia Alix Fillingham, Executive Director (Box 21)
  - Lawyers for Children Conference California, December 17, 1999 2:30-3:15 (Box 21)
  - Lawyers for Childrens Conference (Box 21)
  - Press Conference Washington: Janet Reno June 7, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Carnegie Request (Box 21)
  - Lawyers for Children America Resource Manual and Other Publications (Box 21)
  - The League Treatment Center (Box 21)
  - Leap (Box 21)
  - Learning Disability Experts (Box 21)
  - Kiddush: August 5, 1995, Mishkenot Sha'ananim (Box 22)
  - Boyer Center (Box 22)
  - Molecular Genetics Lab (Box 22)
  - Lu,Xueofen (Box 22)
  - "M" Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Media symposium May 1994 (Box 22)
  - Myths About Test Score Comparisons (Box 22)
  - MHCRC (Statements etc) (Box 22)
  - MHCRC Oversight Visit, April 2, 1992, 8-5:00 PM (Box 22)
  - Marks (Box 22)
  - Marks Proposal: Biochemical Research In Autism (Box 22)
  - Mashentucket Pequot Indians: Early Childhood Collaboration (Box 22)
  - MacArthur, Jan 1 1988 (Box 22)
  - John F. McDermott, MD, Editor Elect, JAACAP (Box 22)
  - The National Academies (Report to the Congress 1997-98) (Box 23)
  - National Academy of Sciences, National Research Council (Box 23)
  - National Center for Clinical Infant Programs, March, 1987, New Haven, CT. (Box 23)
  - National Center for Clinical Infant Programs (Box 23)
  - National Research Council (Box 23)
  - CSC: NAMI Collaboration (Box 23)
  - NCCIP: Directory (Box 23)
  - Korczak-Grant Application " Very Early Direction of Autism" NICHD (Box 23)
  - NICHD Program Project Grant (Box 23)
  - NICHD Site Visit, June 1, 1994 (Box 23)
  - NICHD (Box 23)
  - NICHD Addresses (Box 23)
  - Program Project NICHD, 1989 (Box 23)
  - NICHD: Mental Retardation and Developmental Psychology Overview (Box 23)
  - NICHD Press Release (Box 23)
  - NIHCD Program Project Site Visit, Washington, DC, 1/9/95 (Box 23)
  - NIHCD Memos (Box 23)
  - NIHCD Site Visit (Box 23)
  - NIHCD Biobehavioral Work Group (Box 23)
  - NIHCD Rfp's, Marie Bristol-Powers (Box 23)
  - McLean Hospital (Box 23)
  - Bill McMahon Visit, March 1992 (Box 23)
  - Medical School Bulletin (Box 23)
  - Medical School Bulletin (Box 23)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Evaluation of the Mental Health Services for Youth Project (Box 23)
  - Mental Retardation Center (Box 23)
  - Methodologic Epidemiology for Children and Adolescents (Box 23)
  - NSAC-Autism Research Correlation Proposal (Box 23)
  - NSAC Autopsy Study (Box 23)
  - Congressional Hearings on Human Subject Use. National Society for Autistic Children (Box 23)
  - Fevers-NSAC (Box 23)
  - NSAC Vitamins (Box 23)
  - Medicaid Eligibility (Box 23)
  - NSAC: Social Security Amendments Victoria Raskin: Government Affairs Director (Box 23)
  - Social Security Amendments (Box 24)
  - NSAC-Aversives (Cross Filed with Behavior Research Institute) (Box 24)
  - NSAC-Aversives (Box 24)
  - NSAC, PAB Policy Letter (Box 24)
  - NSAC Professional Advisory Board (Box 24)
  - Anna Freud Center (Box 24)
  - The Impact of Developmental Consideration on the Aims of Child and Adult Psychoanalysis (Box 24)
  - NSAC: Roy Morgan, Executive Director (Box 24)
  - Ms. Susan Morgenstein, Director of Special Exhibition, US Holocaust Memorial Council (Box 24)
  - Munchausen By Proxy-MTG NIMH (Box 24)
  - "N" Miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - New Haven Schools (Box 24)
  - New Haven Board of Education, Office of Assessment and Planning (Box 24)
  - Nosology (Box 24)
  - Negotiation Talks, November 10, 1995, 3:30 pm (Box 24)
  - Panel on Mental Health of Children (Box 24)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 24)
  - New Yorker Magazine (Box 24)
  - Site Visit, Adolescent Programs, Philadelphia, PA, January 3-4 1989 (Box 24)
  - Nova (Box 24)
  - National Crime and Violence Prevention Resource Council (Box 24)
  - Clinical Neuroendocrinology Unit (Box 24)
  - National Commission on Children (The National Academies, Board and Forum Status Report) Jan 2000 (Box 24)
  - National Summit on Children and Families, Washington D.C. April 1-2, 1993 (Box 24)
  - National Commission on Children (Box 24)
  - National Commission on Children, Washington, D.C. June 23, 1989 (Box 24)
  - National Commission on Children, site Visit, May 20-21, 1990 (Box 24)
  - National Commission on Children, Member List (Box 25)
  - National Commission on Children, Travel Expenses (Box 25)
  - National Commission on Children, Travel Worksheets and procedures (Box 25)
  - National Institute of Health (Box 25)
  - National Tuberous Sclerosis Association, Inc (Box 25)
  - Neubauer, Peter B. Director, Child Development Center (Box 25)
  - Neuropsychoanalysis (Box 25)
  - Newberger, Eli H. MD., Director, Family Development Study, The Children's Hospital Medical Center, Boston, Massachusetts. (Box 25)
  - University Advisory Committee, New Haven Education Initiative, December 7, 1994, Corporation Room, Woodbridge Hall (Box 25)
  - Office of Assessment and Planning (Box 25)
  - Kids First Progress Report (Box 25)
  - New Haven Peace Commission (Box 25)
  - Academic Partnerships Between Yale University and Career High School (Box 25)
  - New Haven Public Schools (Box 25)
  - Dropout Prevention Program (Box 25)
  - HUD Development Program, June 6, 1995 (Box 25)
  - Timothy Dwight School (Box 25)
  - CSC/Troup Clinic (Box 25)
  - Dr. Mayo- City of New Haven Community Learning Centers Proposal (Box 25)
  - Wilber Cross-Yale Prep. Program (WC-YPP) (Box 25)
  - NICHD: Clinical Research Project. Tourette's Syndrome (Box 25)
  - NIH: Telephone and service Directory (Box 25)
  - NIMH: Research on Emergency Mental Health Services for Children and Adolescents (Box 25)
  - NIMH: Advancing Research on Developmental Plasticity, Westfield's Conf. Center, May 12-15, 1996 (Box 25)
  - NIMH: Request for Applications (Box 25)
  - NIMH: Child and Adolescent Mental Disorders Research. (Box 25)
  - CSC NIMH Postdoctoral Training Program (Box 25)
  - Program Contacts (Box 25)
  - NIMH Site Visit Construction Grant, September 19, 1989, 9:30-1:00 PM (Box 25)
  - Tuesday Research Seminar, September 5, 1991, 4:30-7:00, April 3, 1992, 1:15-3:00 (Box 25)
  - "O" Miscellaneous (Box 25)
  - OSHA Survey (Box 25)
  - Dan Offord Visit, February 4-5 1992 (Box 25)
  - Oklahoma City Crises (Box 25)
  - ONOCOLOGY: Child survivor Study (Box 25)
  - Obsessive Compulsive Disorder Screening Protocol (Box 25)
  - Orphan Drugs (Box 25)
  - Orphan Drug Grant Proposal, James F. Leckman, MD (Box 25)
  - Jewish Mystical Leadership (Box 25)
  - Anti-Semitism (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous "P", "Q" (Box 26)
  - Melodie Peet (Box 26)
  - Princeton University (Box 26)
  - ProAnima.com: Psychiatric Service on the Iternet (Box 26)
  - Professional Schools' Neighborhood Clinic, June 7, 1996 (Box 26)
  - David Pruitt Visit, May 30, 1995 (Box 26)